# Alix Reyna

**Project Management** 

# **Personal Info**

**Address** 

Río Yaqui 102 Ajijic, Jal.

**Phone** 

Mexico

+52 834 30 11546

E-mail

alixreynaflo@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/alix-reyna-flores-744a6095

## Languages

English - Advanced

Spanish - Native

#### **Certificates**

2020-06

Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)

2019-02

Certificate in Full Stack Javascript Development

2017

ICAgile- ICP Agile Fundamentals

I am an operations & logistics enthusiast that got my start in the world of Esports, first as a content collaborator for ESLA, and later as a logistics guru for Riot Games in the LATAM region. This experience allowed me to collaborate with international teams and leverage technology to improve our work together. I love operations & logistics because I get to leverage my ability to collaborate with others across business units and cultures to enable magical customer experiences.

### **Experience**

2019-01 - **Vendor Management Specialist** 

2020-04 Riot Games - LATAM

Nowadays, I am primarily focused on supporting financial and legal operations and international logistics. As a certified full stack developer, I am also involved in advising the development of internal tools and processes that can help improve the employee experience when developing new projects and making purchasing decisions for the company.

2018-04 - Office Coordinator

2018-12 Riot Games - LATAM

Over time, my responsibilities at the Riot Games LATAM office expanded to include support for the Santiago, Chile office. As Office Coordinator, I was tasked with providing logistics services that accommodated internal and player facing projects for multiple interdisciplinary teams in two offices across the LATAM region. My biggest learning during this time was in being able to work with distributed teams across multiple time zones in a global scale.

2016-05 - Office Assistant

2018-04 Riot Games - Latin America North

I originally joined Riot in an administrative role, where I was responsible for employee (rioter) travel and virtual live event logistics, legal documentation tracking and storage, and supported live events and larger multimedia campaigns.

2015 - **Content Collaborator** 

2016 Esports Latinoamerica (ESLA)

I got my start as a Content Collaborator, managing esports even logistics and coaching shoutcasters to improve their public speaking and presentation skills within the context of Esports hosting livestream. 5+ shoutcasters that I coached went onto bigger hosting opportunities at places like Riot Games, Activision Blizzard Nintendo, and others.

#### **Education**

2013 - **Universidad La Salle Victoria -** Cum Laude Bachelor's

I graduated with top honors in Communications Science, with a specialization on the effects of Mass Communication.